A Guide to the University of Virginia Hospital Executive Director's Office (HEDO) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- GERIATRICS-ONCOLOGY UNIT (BLUE RIDGE): CENTER FOR HEALTH OF THE ELDERLY August 1981, TMs (Box-folder 40:009)
- GERIATRICS-ONCOLOGY UNIT (BLUE RIDGE): CORRESPONDENCE 1981 - 1983, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 40:010)
- GERIATRICS-ONCOLOGY UNIT (BLUE RIDGE): DEMONSTRATION NURSING CARE UNIT PROPOSAL October 1981, TMs (Box-folder 40:011)
- GERIATRICS-ONCOLOGY UNIT (BLUE RIDGE): GERIATRIC/REHABILITATION UNIT PROPOSAL August 1982, TMs (Box-folder 40:012)
- GERIATRICS-ONCOLOGY UNIT (BLUE RIDGE): SKILLED NIRSING FACILITY PROPOSAL 1981 - 1982, TMs (Box-folder 40:013)
- LITHOTRIPTER: CORRESPONDENCE 1983 - 1984, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 40:014)
- LITHOTRIPTER: CORRESPONDENCE 1985, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 40:015)
- LITHOTRIPTER: CORRESPONDENCE 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 40:016)
- LITHOTRIPTER: CORRESPONDENCE 1987, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 40:017)
- LITHOTRIPTER: LITHOTRIPSY SYSTEMS TECHNOLOGY UPDATE April 1988, TMs (Box-folder 40:018)
- LITHOTRIPTER: NATIONAL HEALTH SERVICES COST AND PAYMENT ANALYSIS January 1986, TMs (Box-folder 40:019)
- LITHOTRIPTER: NHSPPS PERCUTANEOUS LITHOTRIPSY OPERATING COSTS STUDY February 1986, TMs (Box-folder 40:020)
- LITHOTRIPTER: PROPAC REVIEW OF LITHOTRIPSY January 1986, TMs (Box-folder 40:021)
- LITHOTRIPTER: PROPOSED LITHOTRIPER REGULATION February 1987, TMs (Box-folder 40:022)
- MAGNETIC RESONANCE IMAGING: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1982, TLS TMs (Box-folder 41:001)
- MAGNETIC RESONANCE IMAGING: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1983 - 1984, TLS, TMs, Newsclipping (Box-folder 41:002)
- MAGNETIC RESONANCE IMAGING: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1985 - 1988, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 41:003)
- MAGNETIC RESONANCE IMAGING:DRAF6T REPLANNING JUSTIFICATION FOR NMR August 1982, TMs (Box-folder 41:004)
- MAGNETIC PERSONAL IMAGING: INTERIM MRI MACHINE PURCHASE PROPOSAL November 1988, TMs (Box-folder 41:005)
- MAGNETIC RESONANCE IMAGING: MRI CERTIFICATE OF PUBLIC NEED August 1988, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 41:006)
- MAGNETIC RESONANCE IMAGING: MRI CERTIFICATE OF PUBLIC NEED February 1989, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 41:007)
- MAGNETIC RESONANCE IMAGING: MRI UNIT ANALYSIS November 1985, TMs (Box-folder 41:008)
- MAGNETIC RESONANCE IMAGING: MRI AMENDMENTS TO THE STATE HEALTH MAN July 1984, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 41:009)
- MAGNETIC RESONANCE IMAGING: SITE LOCATION STUDY August 1982, TMs (Box-folder 41:010)
- MEDICAL CENTER DEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1972, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 41:011)
- MEDICAL CENTER DEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1972, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 41:012)
- MEDICAL CENTER DEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1973, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 41:013)
- MEDICAL CENTER DEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1974, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 41:014)
- MEDICAL CENTER DEVELOPMENT COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1973 - 1974, TMs (Box-folder 41:015)
- POSITION APPEALS: UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL February 1982-March 1982, TLS (Box-folder 41:016)
- PROPOSAL FOR SURGICAL SUITE ANALYSIS October 1985, TMs (Box-folder 42:001)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MINUTES 1985, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 42:002)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MINUTES August 1985, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 42:003)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MINUTES 1986, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 42:004)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MINUTES 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 42:005)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MINUTES 1987, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 42:006)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MINUTES 1987, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 42:007)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MINUTES 1987, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 42:008)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MINUTES December 1987, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 43:001)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MINUTES 1988 - 1989, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 43:002)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: MASTER PROJECT CONTROL PLAN 1985 - 1986, TMs (Box-folder 43:003)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: PROGRESS REPORTS 1985, TMs (Box-folder 43:004)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: PROGRESS REPORTS 1986, TMs (Box-folder 43:005)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: PROGRESS REPORTS 1986, TMs (Box-folder 43:006)
- BLUE RIDGE HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE, MINUTES AND REPORT 1984 - 1985, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 44:001)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1892 - 1913, AMs (Box-folder 44:002)
  ORIGINAL BOUND BOOK WITH HANDWRITTEN NOTES
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1892 - 1905, AMs, Typed Transcript (Box-folder 44:003)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1905 - 1913, AMs, Transcripts (Box-folder 44:004)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1913 - 1919, Typed Transcript (Box-folder 44:005)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1913 - 1919, Typed Transcript (Box-folder 44:006)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1913 - 1919, AMs (Box-folder 44:007)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1941 - 1943, TMs (Box-folder 45:005)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1939 - 1943, TMs (Box-folder 45:004)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1920 - 1941, TMs (Box-folder 45:003)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1931 - 1938, TMs (Box-folder 45:002)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1920 - 1930, TMs (Box-folder 45:001)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1943 - 1945, TL, TMs (Box-folder 46:001)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1943 - 1945, TMs (Box-folder 46:002)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1946 - 1949, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 46:003)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1946 - 1949, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 46:004)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1950 - 1953, TMs (Box-folder 46:005)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: MINUTES 1950 - 1953, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 46:006)
- MEDICAL FACULTY: REPORT ON ATHLETIC COMMITTEE REPORT Ca 1949, TMs (Box-folder 46:007)
- MEDICAL SCHOOL: CONSTITUTION PROPOSED AMENDMENTS, SIGNATURES AND CORRESPONDENCE 1936 - 1938, 1946 - 1947, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 46:008)
- MEDICAL SCHOOL: CONSTITUTION, PROPOSED AMENDMENTS, SIGNATURES AND CORRESPONDENCE 1936 - 1938, 1946 - 1947, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 46:009)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND REPORTS 1981, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 47:001)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND REPORTS 1982, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 47:002)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND REPORTS 1982, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 47:003)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND REPORTS 1983, TMs, Articles (Box-folder 47:004)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE AND REPORTS 1984, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 47:005)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: LONG RANGE PLAN June 1982, TMs (Box-folder 47:006)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: LONG RANGE PLAN January 1983, TMs (Box-folder 47:007)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: LONG RANGE PLAN September 1983, TMs (Box-folder 47:008)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: LONG RANGE PLAN UPDATE March 1984, TMs (Box-folder 47:009)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: PRESENTATION TO SMA January 1982, TMs (Box-folder 47:010)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: PROGRAM PROPOSAL March 1983, TMs (Box-folder 47:011)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLNNING COMMITTEE: STATEMENT OF MISSION, GOALS... 1984 - 1986, TMs (Box-folder 47:012)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: LICENSE APPLICATION December 1986, TL, TMs (Box-folder 48:001)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: MANAGEMENT CONTRACT November 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 48:002)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: MANAGEMENT SALES AGREEMENT October 1986, TMs (Box-folder 48:003)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: REVISED COMPENSATION MECHANISM FOR CHARLOTTESVILLE AREA PROVIDERS November 1986, TLS, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 48:004)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PROVIDERS: MINUTES April 1987, TMs (Box-folder 48:005)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: MINUTES May 1987, TMs (Box-folder 48:006)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: MINUTES May, June 1987, TMs (Box-folder 48:007)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: PRESENTATIONS January, February 1987, TMs (Box-folder 48:008)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: REQUEST FOR PROPOSAL May, June 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 48:009)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: STATEWIDE HMO EMPLOYER SURVEY AND INTERVIEW DATA October 1986, TMs (Box-folder 48:010)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: CORRESPONDENCE 1986 - 1987, TLS, TMs, TL, AMs (Box-folder 49:001)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: CORRESPONDENCE 1987, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 49:002)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: DEVELOPEMENT AND MANAGEMENT AGREEMENT December 1986, TLs, TLS (Box-folder 49:003)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: DEVELOPMENT AND MANAGEMENT AGREEMENT December 1986, TMs (Box-folder 49:004)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: DEVELOPMENT AND MANAGEMENT AGREEMENT June 1987, TMs (Box-folder 49:005)
- VIEGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: EXECUTIVE SUMMARY OF LEGAL DOCUMENTS Janaury 1987, TMs (Box-folder 49:006)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: FEASILILITY STUDY FOR A PREPAID HEALTH PLAN April 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 49:007)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: FINANCIAL STATEMENTS October 1986, TMs (Box-folder 49:008)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: FINANCIAL STATEMENTS Novemebr 1986, TMs (Box-folder 49:009)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: FINANCIAL STATEMENTS March 1987, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 49:010)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: HMO DEVELOPMENT PROPOSAL June 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 49:011)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: JOINT COMMITTEE ON ALTERNATIVE DELIVERY SYSTEM-CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1985 - 1986, TLS, TMs, AMs, News Articles (Box-folder 49:012)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: ALTERNATIVE DELIVERY SYSTEMS COMMITTEE REPORT AND ATTACHED LETTERS October 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 50:001)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: ARTICLES OF INCORPORATION AND BYLAWS October 1987, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 50:002)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: ARTICLES OF INCORPORATION AND BYLAWS November 1986, TMs (Box-folder 50:003)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: ARTICLES OF INCORPORATION AND BYLAWS December 1986, TMs (Box-folder 50:004)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: ARTICLES OF INCORPORATION AND BYLAWS December 1986, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 50:005)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: ARTICLES OF INCORPORATION AND BYLAWS DRAFT December 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 50:006)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: ARTICLES OF INCORPORATION AND BYLAWS March 1987, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 50:007)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: BUSINESS CONCEPT September 1986, TMs (Box-folder 50:008)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: CHARLOTTESVILLE AREA ALTERNATIVE DELIVERY SYSTEM FEASIBILITY July 1986, TMs (Box-folder 50:009)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: CHARLOTTESVILLE AREA ALTERNATIVE DELIVERY SYSTEM FEASIBILITY STUDY-KEY FINDINGS September 1986, TLS (Box-folder 50:010)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: CONCEPT MEMORANDUM February 1986, TMs (Box-folder 50:011)
  PREPARED FOR MARTHA JEFFERSON HOSPITAL AND UVA HOSPITAL
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: CORRESPONDENCE 1986, TLS, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 50:012)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: CORRESPONDENCE 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 50:013)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: CORRESPONDENCE 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 50:014)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: STATEWIDE HMO FEASIBILITY September 1986, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 51:001)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: STATEWIDE HMO FEASIBILITY October 1986, TMs (Box-folder 51:002)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: STATEWIDE HMO FEASIBILITY November 1986, TMs (Box-folder 51:003)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: SUMMARY OF FEASIBILITY FINDINGS September 1986, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 51:004)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: SUMMARY OF FEASIBILITY FINDINGS September 1986, TMs (Box-folder 51:005)
- VIRGINIA HEALTH PARTNERS: SUMMARY OF FEASIBILITY FINDINGS October 1986, TMs (Box-folder 51:006)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL PROJECT: MINUTES 1985 - 1988, TMs (Box-folder 52:001)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL AND RELATED FACILITIES EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE BUILDING COMMITTEE February 21, 1985, TMs (Box-folder 52:002)
- ARCHITECTURAL DESIGN REVIEW SUBCOMMITTEE: REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL October 1983-October 1984, TL, TMs (Box-folder 52:003)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE AND DOCUMENTS: HOSPITAL REPLACEMENT PROJECT November 1988 - May 1989, TL, TMs (Box-folder 52:004)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL AND RELATED FACILITIES EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE MEETING July 1988 - March 1989, TMs (Box-folder 52:005)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE AND DOCUMENTS: HOSPITAL REPLACEMENT PROJECT October - December 1984, TL, TMs (Box-folder 52:006)
- PROJECTED FINANCIAL STATEMENTS AND REFUNDING ISSUE PROJECTIONS Sept. 1984 - Feb. 1985, TMs (Box-folder 54:001)
  HOSPITAL REPLACEMENT PROJECT
- PROPOSAL FOR MODIFICATION OF THE REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL AND RELATED FACILITIES PROJECT September 25, 1987, TMs (Box-folder 54:002)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL FACT SHEET Aug. 1981 - Feb. 1987, TMs (Box-folder 54:003)
- MISCELLANEOUS DOCUMENTS AND CORRESPONDENCE August 1984 - May 1985, TL, TMs (Box-folder 54:004)
- MISCELLANEOUS DOCUMENTS AND CORRESPONDENCE Feb. 1984 - Jan. 1985, TL, TMs (Box-folder 54:005)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE AND DOCUMENTS Jan. 1983 - March 1984, TMs (Box-folder 54:006)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE AND DOCUMENTS Feb. 1984 - Dec. 1984, TL, TMs (Box-folder 54:007)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE AND DOCUMENTS November 1983 - May 1984, TL, TMs (Box-folder 54:008)
- LEGISLATURE REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL July 1982 - May 1984, TL, TMs (Box-folder 55:001)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL ACTION TEAM May 1982 - August 1983, TL, TMs (Box-folder 55:002)
- PRODUCTIVITY REVIEW--A.D. LITTLE April 27, 1983, TMs (Box-folder 55:003)
  UVA REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL PREPARATION
- FINANCIAL FEASIBILITY REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL PROJECT May 1983 - October 1983, TMs (Box-folder 55:004)
- FINANCIAL FEASIBILITY OF REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL PROJECT June 1982 - March 1983, TMs (Box-folder 55:005)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL REQUEST FOR PROPOSAL Feb. 1981 - Sept. 1982, TMs, TL (Box-folder 55:006)
- HOSPITAL REPLACEMENT PROJECT: CORRESPONDENCE AND DOCUMENTS July 1980 - October 1982, TL, TMs (Box-folder 56:001)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL PROJECT: PROGRAMMING SUBCOMMITTEE May 1982 - February 1984, TL, TMs (Box-folder 56:002)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL COMMITTEE: PLANNING COMMITTEE June 1982 - March 1983, TL, TMs (Box-folder 56:003)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL BUILDING COMMITTEE November 1982 - June 1984, TL, TMs (Box-folder 57:001)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL CERTIFICATE OF NEED July 1983 - April 1984, TL, TMs (Box-folder 57:002)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: ARCHITECTURAL SELECTION COMMITTEE Oct. 1982 - Dec. 1982, TL, TMs (Box-folder 57:003)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: CONSTRUCTION MANAGER REQUEST FOR PROPOSAL December 1983 - May 1985, TL, TMs (Box-folder 57:004)
- HOSPITAL REPLACEMENT PROJECT: CORESPONDENCE AND DOCUMENTS FOR FINANCIAL FEASIBILITY AND PLANNING Oct. 1984 - Nov. 1985, TMs (Box-folder 58:001)
- HOSPITAL REPLACEMENT PROJECT: CORRESPONDENCE AND DOCUMENTS Oct. 1984 - Nov. 1985, TMs (Box-folder 58:002)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL AND RELATED FACILITIES December 14, 1984, Blueprint (Box-folder 58:003)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL November 24, 1986, TMs (Box-folder 59:001)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL September 1987, TMs (Box-folder 59:002)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL January 1988 - June 1988, TMs (Box-folder 59:003)
- REPLACEMENT HOSPITAL: PLANNING BACKGROUND DATA March 5, 1982, TMs (Box-folder 59:004)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLAN 1983 - 1990 January 1984, TM (Box-folder 59:005)
- UVA HOSPITAL: PLANNING ASSUMPTIONS AND LONG RANGE PLANS March 1982 - March 1985, TMemo, TM (10) (Box-folder 60:001)
- UVA HOSPITAL LONG RANGE PLAN June 1982 - March 1985, TM (3) (Box-folder 60:002)
- LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1981 - 1982, TMs (Box-folder 60:003)
- LONG RANGE PLANNING COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1983 - 1984, TMs (Box-folder 60:004)
- BLUE RIDGE HOSPITAL: LONG RANGE PLANNING CONFERECE March 5, 1982, TMemo, TMs, Article Offprint, TL (Box-folder 60:005)
- OVERTIME PAYMENT 1925-1946, 2 DOC (Box-folder 60:006)
- BLUE RIDGE COMPREHENSIVE COMMUNITY MENTAL HEALTH CENTER 1970-1974, 5 TD, 4 TLS (Box-folder 60:007)
- American College of Surgeons Hospital Standardization Scoring Report, UVa Hospital ( Precursor to Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals) 1948, 1 TDS with AN (Box-folder 61:001)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1953, 1 TDS (Box-folder 61:002)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1954, 1 TDS, 1 TLS (Box-folder 61:003)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1957, 1 TD with AN, 1 TD with AN copy, 1 TD with AN copy partial, 2TL copy, 1 TLS (Box-folder 61:004)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1959, 1 TLs copy, 1 Tmemo, 2 TLS (Box-folder 61:005)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1960, 1 TD with AN, 1 TLS copy (Box-folder 61:006)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1963, 1 TLS (Box-folder 61:007)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1966, 2 TD, 1 TD with AN, 1 TL copy, 3 memos, 2 TLS (Box-folder 61:008)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1969, 1 TD, 1 TL copy, 1 Tmemo, 1 TLS (Box-folder 61:009)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1970, 2 TLS (Box-folder 61:010)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1971, 1 TD copy, 1 journal article fragment (Box-folder 61:011)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1972, 1 TD with AN, 1 TD copy, 3 TL copy (Box-folder 61:012)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1973, 5 TD copy with AN, 1 TLS, 1 memo, 5 TLS copy, 1 brochure (Box-folder 61:013)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1974, 1 TD, 1 TD copy, 2 TLS copy, 2 TLS, 3TD with AN, 1 TDS copy (Box-folder 61:014)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1975, 1 TLS (Box-folder 61:015)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1976, 3 TD copy, 1 TLS copy, 2 brochures, 3 TLS (Box-folder 61:016)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1977, 2 TD, 1 TDS copy, 1 TD with AN, 1 TD copy, 1 memo, 2 TLS (Box-folder 61:017)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1978, 2 TD, 1 TDS, 2 TD copy, 2 TLS copy (Box-folder 61:018)
- Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, UVa Hospital 1979, 2 TD copy, 2 TD, 1 TL copy, 1 envelope, 1 TD with AN, 1 TLS, 1 Tmemo copy, 3 TLS copy (Box-folder 61:019)